[Strings]
title = "WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SHARE\?"
game_variant = "GAME VARIANT"
game_variant_description = "This lists all of your saved game variants. Visit Custom Games to create new game variants to share."
map_variant = "MAP VARIANT"
map_variant_description = "This lists all of your saved map variants. Visit the Forge to create new map variants to share."
film = "FILM"
film_description = "This lists all of your saved films. Play games in Campaign and Firefight to build a library of films to share."
film_clip = "FILM CLIP"
film_clip_description = "This lists all of your saved film clips. Record clips from any multiplayer film to build a library of film clips to share."
screenshot = "SCREENSHOT"
screenshot_description = "This lists all of your saved screenshots. Take screenshots from any film to build a library of screenshots to share."
unused_quota_used = "<quota-used/>"
unused_quota_total = "<quota-total/>"
quota_remaining = "<quota-remaining/> free in your File Share."
